#!/bin/bash
#
# Copyright (c) 2013, Markus Alexander Kuppe
# All rights reserved.
#
# Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions are met:
#
#    Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.
#    Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer 
#    in the documentation and/or other materials provided with the distribution.
#    Neither the name of the <ORGANIZATION> nor the names of its contributors may be used to endorse or promote products derived 
#    from this software without specific prior written permission.
#
# THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE COPYRIGHT HOLDERS AND CONTRIBUTORS "AS IS" AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO,
# THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE COPYRIGHT HOLDER OR 
# CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT
# OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN
# CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED 
# OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.
#

# Who we are
DIRNAME=`dirname $0`
BASENAME=`basename $0`
NOW=`date +%s`

# Switch to folder where this request originated from an search for p2 repositories in subdirectories
# A p2 repository qualifies, if an artifacts.xml|jar file can be found (expecting either artifacts.xml or zipped artifacts.jar)
# This is obviously the performance bottleneck and thus uses min/max depth as a restriction
cd $DIRNAME
REPOS=`find */builds -mindepth 5 -maxdepth 8 -type f -iname artifacts.xml -o -iname artifacts.jar -printf "%h\n"`

# (remember quotes matter!)
AMOUNT=`echo "$REPOS" | wc -l`

# print required first line
echo "Content-type: text/xml";
echo "";
echo "<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>";

# print content or artifact header depending on request
if [ $BASENAME == "compositeArtifacts.xml" ]
then
echo "<?compositeArtifactRepository version='1.0.0'?>
<repository name='CI ArtifactRepository' type='org.eclipse.equinox.internal.p2.artifact.repository.CompositeArtifactRepository' version='1.0.0'>";
else 
echo "<?compositeMetadataRepository version='1.0.0'?>
<repository name='CI MetadataRepository' type='org.eclipse.equinox.internal.p2.metadata.repository.CompositeMetadataRepository' version='1.0.0'>";
fi

# print properties
echo "<properties size='2'><property name='p2.compressed' value='true'/><property name='p2.timestamp' value='$NOW'/></properties>";

# print number of children
echo "<children size='$AMOUNT'>";

# print child repos
for repo in $REPOS
do
    echo "<child location='$repo/'/>";
done

# print footer
echo "</children></repository>";


